

Applicant for:

Software Developer (.NET, Java, MySQL)

VNPOST 15 September 2019

Hoàng Long

☑ danhlongit@gmail.com

Main interests: .NET, C#

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Dear!

I know that the company are recruiting at the position: Programmer

This is very consistent job with my ability and experience which have been summarized in the learning process as well as working process. So i respectfully submit to the company to ask for entrance. I am waiting to receive information and feedback from company. Please contact to me. My phone number is 0977377083

PROFILE

OF HOANG DANH LONG

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name HOANG DANH LONG

Nationality Vietnamese

Date of Birth May 14, 1991

Sex Male

Marital Status Married

Mail danhlongit@gmail.com

Mobile 0977377083

Address No. 346 – Nam Du – Hoang Mai – Ha Noi

LANGUAGES

Vietnamese Mother tongue

English Fair

EDUCATION

• 2002-2006 Quynh Bang Junior High School

• 2006-2009 **Quynh Luu 3 High School**

• 2009-2014 Vinh University

WORKING EXPERIENCE

From 2014 to Current Year

Position: Developer (from 3/2014 to now)

Organization: Vietcombank

SUMMARY

Graduated at 2014. In university, participate in bulding managing finance software and hospital managing software on C# / MFC C++ flatform

PRACTICAL EXPERIENCE SINCE 2014

Technical skills:

OPERATING SYSTEMS

- Windows XP/Windows Vista
- Windows Server 2012
- Windows 7,8,10
- Linux (CentOS ,Ubuntu)

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES, APP FRAMEWORKS, & TOOLS

- C/C++
- C#
- HTML, JavaScript
- SQL
- PostgreSQL
- MySQL
- Oracle
- MongoDB

DATABASES

- SQL server 2014
- Oracle
- PostgreSQL
- MySQL
- MongoDB

DATA COMMUNICATIONS & NETWORKS

- TCP/IP
- LAN, VLAN

	software	
Position(s)	Developer	1/3/2014 to
		01/11/2014

General information

Customer: Central army hospital 108

Team Size: 25 people

Project size: 8 month

Description

- Program the hospital managing software based on description about ORACLE database standardized by C#/MFC C++ language.

Project Scope

The scope is:

Requirement studyDetail Design (DS)

- Coding & Unit testing (P).

- Create report

- Deploy

Technology used

Run-time environment

Microsoft Windows 7

Oracle database.

Development environment

Microsoft Windows 7

Oracle database.

VPS server

MFC

Project name	Building hospital managing software	Duration	
Position(s)	Developer	05-11-2014 to 01-3-2016	
General	Customer: Me Linh hospital.Team Size: 3 people		
information			
	Project size : 1 year		
Description	- Program the hospital managing software based on description		
	about SQL database standardized by MVC C# language.		
Project Scope	The scope is:		
	- Requirement study		
	- Detail Design (DS)		
	- Coding & Unit testing (P).		
	- Create report		
	- Deploy		
Technology	Run-time environment		
used	Microsoft Windows 7		
	Oracle database.		
	Development environment		
	Microsoft Windows 7		
	 Oracle database. 		
	VPS Server		
	■ Asp.net, MVC 5		
	Entity framework		

Project name	HP-GL/2 and HP RTL	Duration
Position(s)	Developer	01-03-2016 to10/05/2016
General information	 Customer: Japan customer. Team Size: 12 people 	
Description	 Project size: 3 month Fix bug HPGL C++ 	
	-	
Project Scope	- Code	
	- Fix bug	
Technology	Run-time environment	
used	Microsoft Windows 7,8,10	
	 Microsoft XP/Vista 	
	 Microsoft Server 2003,2008,2 	012
	Development environment	
	Microsoft Windows 7	
	 Visual studio 15 	
	• C++	
1	Framework .NET 2.0	

Project name	Dell Color Multifunction Printer	Duration
Position(s)	Developer	15-05-2016 to 15-10-2016
General	Customer: FX (Japan).	
information		
	Team Size: 2 people	
	Project size: 5 month	
Description	- Detail Design ,Coding Screen Main Menu,Software Installation,Support	
	Tools (MFC C++)	
Project Scope	- Create Detail Design	
	- Coding	
Technology	Run-time environment	
used	■ Microsoft Windows 7,8,10	
	■ Microsoft XP/Vista	
	■ Microsoft Server 2003,2008,2012	
	Development environment	
	Microsoft Windows 7	
	Visual studio 15	
	■ MFC C++	

Project name	Building hospital managing software	Duration	
Position(s)	Developer	10 -2016 – 09-2017	
General	Customer: Vietnam national cancer hospital		
information	·		
	Team Size: 17 people		
	Project size: 3 year		
Description	- Program the hospital managing software based on description about		
	Oracle database standardized by MVC C# language.		
Project Scope	The scope is:		
	- Requirement study		
	- Detail Design (DS)		
	- Coding & Unit testing (P).		
	- Create report		
	- Deploy		
Technology	Run-time environment		
used	Microsoft Windows 7		
	 Oracle database. 		
	Development environment		
	Microsoft Windows 7		
	 Oracle database. 		
	VPS Server		
	• Asp.net, MVC 5		
	 Entity framework 		

Project name	Teller For Signature (CoreBanking)	Duration	
Position(s)	Developer	09 -2017 to now	
General	Customer: Vietcombank		
information	Team Size: 17 people		
	Project size: 3 year		
Description	- Bank requests for Prepaid Interest Time Deposit product.		
	- For Cash Transfer Out and Cash Transfer In, after user enter the To		
	Teller ID or From Teller ID, VCB requires system to show the name of		
	the Teller ID entered.		
	- VCB requires system to cater for 2 different cash exchange rate for a		
	currency:		
	+ Big Denomination		
	+ Small Denomination		
	- VCB require that no exchange rate change should go beyond variance.		
	Not even supervisor can exceed variance		
	- Modification support the requirements of the client		
	SQL database standardized by C# language.		
Project Scope	The scope is:		
	- Requirement study ,FSD,TSD		
	- Coding & Unit testing (P).		
	- Fix bug		
	- Support		
Technology	Run-time environment		
used	 Microsoft Windows 7 (Environment Singapore) 		
	 SQL database. 		
	Development environment		
	 Microsoft Windows 7 (Environment Singapore) 		
	 SQL database. 		
	VPS Server		

Music, football ...